but as the night went on I realized it
didn't matter why they were here we were
both getting what we wanted I got to
work through my nervousness around women
sorry I'm kind of shaking don't be
nervous don't be nervous that's so cute
and they got to be on TV I would love to
have everyone introduced to kingan water
this water is one of the best Waters out
there it has a pH of 9.5 I'd never been
that good of a flirt but I had the
opportunity to practice with so many
beautiful girls you have beautiful eyes
and beautiful lips and lovely hair and
your style
is
wonderful
oh thanks
mate so tell me your deepest darkest
secret my deepest darkest secret
is
I don't like wearing
socks that's great but as the night
progressed oh cool magic my flirting
skills drastically improved do you ride
motorcycles I mean I don't ride a
motorcycle but I am a bit of a bad boy
but what happened next I would have
never
expected